<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <integer-array name="ourPictures">
        <item>@drawable/image11</item>
        <item>@drawable/image2</item>
        <item>@drawable/image3</item>
        <item>@drawable/image4</item>
        <item>@drawable/image17</item>
        <item>@drawable/image14</item>
        <item>@drawable/image5</item>
        <item>@drawable/image7</item>
        <item>@drawable/image8</item>
        <item>@drawable/image10</item>
        <item>@drawable/image16</item>
        <item>@drawable/image12</item>
        <item>@drawable/image13</item>
        <item>@drawable/image15</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="captions">
        <item>Cuban and Mexican. \n Masters in CS. \n Friends call me Richie.</item>
        <item>Thanks for dancing with me on Halloween.</item>
        <item>Thanks for going out with me after realizing I couldn\'t dance. </item>
        <item>More importantly, thanks for dealing with my bad photography skills and sense of humor.</item>
        <item>Like omg we are super cute together. Like Literally. I can\'t even. #TeamLourdesAndRichie </item>
        <item>It was so hard to make this, my eyes kept tearing up.</item>
        <item>I\'m grateful for meeting all your friends and introducing you to my own.</item>
        <item>I enjoyed having a nice cuddle buddy this Winter with a nice butt.</item>
        <item>Having a date to go out to eat yummy food with.</item>
        <item>I even enjoyed being dragged out to things I never would do.</item>
        <item>Thanks for taking the chance to move here. Chicago is lucky to have you and so am I.</item>
        <item>Te quiero no solo por como eres, sino por como soy yo cuando estoy contigo</item>
        <item>Tardé una hora en conocerte y solo un día en enamorarme. Pero me llevará toda una vida lograr olvidarte.</item>
        <item>Happy Birthday Lourdes!\nI can\'t thank you enough for being in my life. You have a great, kind heart and you make me feel so special.
        I can\'t think of anyone who\'s made me feel the way you have made me feel. The moments we\'ve had together and the ones we will experience will be worth
        whatever the future has to offer. I love you.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>